Guide to the Richard Kelly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project files, 1939-1977; Series I
  - State Museum of Archives, Art, State, and Natural History, 1950
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 79)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 79)
  - State University, Stony Brook
    Job location: Stony Brook, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 79)
  - Stephens College, 1960
    Job location: Columbia, MO
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 313)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 313)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 313)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 313)
  - Stork Club, 1941
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 79)
  - Stroheim & Romann, 1955
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 79)
  - Strohl Apartment, 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 79)
  - Sugar Loaf Mountain, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 79)
    - Drawings (Box 79, Box 136)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 79)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 136)
  - Sun Life Insurance Company, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 80)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 80)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 80)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 80)
  - Sunshine Home
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 412)
  - Survey Plan
    - Drawings (Box 281)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 281)
  - Sweeney, Elsie Residence, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings (Box 121, Box 366)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 121)
  - Tel Aviv Municipal Museum, 1965
    Job location: Tel Aviv, IL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
  - Temple Emanu-el, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 80)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 80)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 80)
  - Temple Emanu-el, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 80, Box 387)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 80, Box 387)
  - Thayer, Nat B. House, 1970
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80, Box 407)
    - Drawings (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 407)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 80, Box 407)
  - Theater -- Unidentified
    - Drawings (Box 80)
  - Theater for Loch Edge
    - Drawings (Box 122)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 122)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 122)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 122)
  - Third Church of Christ Scienrtisr, 1972
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 407)
  - Thom, E.R. Residence, 1959
    Job location: Jamaica, West Indies
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 80)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 237)
  - Thomas Crane Public Library, 1963
    Job location: Quincy, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
  - Thompson, J. Walter Company (See Also: J. Walter Thompson Company), 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Box 81, Box 155)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 81)
  - Tiffany and Company, 1940
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 81)
  - Time Inc., 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 81)
  - Timken Fine Arts Gallery (See also: San Diego Fine Arts Gallery), 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Box 146, Box 263, Box 285A, Box 297)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 81, Box 146, Box 297)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 146)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 285A)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 263, Box 285A)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 263, Box 298)
    - Photographs (Box 81)
  - Titus Manufacturing Corporation, 1963
    Job location: Waterloo, IA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 81)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 81)
  - Torno Apartment
    Job location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
    - Drawings (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 81)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 81)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 81)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 81)
  - Toronto City Hall, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81, Box 408)
    - Drawings (Box 138–139, Box 177, Box 206, Box 239–240, Box 375)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 177, Box 408)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 239)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 206, Box 239–240, Box 375, Box 408)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 138–139, Box 189, Box 206, Box 239–240)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 138–139, Box 206, Box 239)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 189, Box 240)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 138–139)
  - Towbin, Belmont Apartment, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81)
  - Travelers Insurance Company, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 81–82, Box 408)
    - Drawings (Box 81–82, Box 127, Box 137, Box 140, Box 153, Box 162, Box 209, Box 219, Box 228, Box 230, Box 248, Box 267, Box 280, Box 296, Box 325, Box 328)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 190, Box 219, Box 267, Box 325, Box 408)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 81–82, Box 190, Box 219, Box 267, Box 325, Box 328)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 127, Box 137, Box 140, Box 153, Box 162, Box 190, Box 209, Box 219, Box 228, Box 248, Box 267, Box 408)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 127, Box 137, Box 140, Box 153, Box 190, Box 209, Box 219, Box 228, Box 248, Box 280, Box 296, Box 328, Box 408)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 127, Box 140, Box 153, Box 162, Box 209, Box 228, Box 280, Box 296, Box 328)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 137, Box 228, Box 248, Box 296)
    - Photographs (Box 408)
  - Tremaine Barn, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
    - Drawings (Box 82)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 82)
  - Trier, Mr. Shadow Box, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
    - Drawings (Box 82)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 82)
  - Trinity Episcopal Church, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
    - Drawings (Box 133)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 82)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 133)
    - Photographs (Box 82)
  - Tulane University, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
  - Tuttle, Wylie Residence, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
  - UNESCO Building, 1958
    Job location: Paris, France
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
  - Union Building Corporation, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
    - Drawings (Box 82)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 82)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 82)
  - Union Carbide and Carbon Corporation Building (See also: Kelly, Richard Offices), 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
    - Drawings (Box 82)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 82)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 82)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 82)
  - Union Idemnity Building, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 82)
    - Drawings (Box 82)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 82)
  - United Engineering Center, 1961
    - Drawings (Box 160)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 160)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 160)
  - United Illuminating Company, 1965
    Job location: Bridgeport, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 83)
    - Drawings (Box 83, Box 228, Box 323, Box 326)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 83, Box 228, Box 326)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 83, Box 228, Box 323)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 323)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 323)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 323, Box 326)
  - United States Naval Academy, Michelson Hall, 1965
    Job location: Annapolis, MD
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 83)
    - Drawings (Box 83, Box 193, Box 242, Box 269, Box 271)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 83)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 242, Box 269, Box 271)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 83, Box 193, Box 242, Box 269)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 193, Box 269)
  - University of Florida
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 83)
  - University of Hartford, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 83)
    - Drawings (Box 83, Box 277)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 83)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 83)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 83)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 83, Box 277)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 83, Box 277)
  - University of Illinois, 1963
    Job location: Illinois
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 83)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1971
    - Drawings (Box 408)
  - University of Texas, 1965
    Job location: Texas
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 83)
    - Drawings (Box 151, Box 215, Box 247)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 151, Box 215, Box 247)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 151, Box 215, Box 247)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 151)
    - Material Samples (Box 83)
  - University of Virginia
    Job location: Charlottesville, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 83, Box 408)
    - Drawings (Box 408)
  - University of Washington
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 84)
    - Drawings (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 84)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 84)
  - Upjohn Company
    Job location: Kalamazoo, MI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 40)
    - Drawings (Box 40)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 40)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 40)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 40)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 40)
  - Ussishkin Hall, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 84)
    - Drawings (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 84, Box 388)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 84, Box 388)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 388)
  - Utica Museum (See Also:Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute), 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 84)
    - Drawings (Box 84, Box 229)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 84)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 84, Box 229, Box 388)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 84, Box 229)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 84, Box 229)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 84)
    - Photographs (Box 84)
  - Vaisey, John Apartment, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 85)
    - Drawings (Box 155, Box 237)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 155, Box 237)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 155)
  - Van Gogh Correspondence, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 85)
  - Van Meter Residence
    Job location: Springfield, IL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 85)
    - Drawings (Box 85, Box 147, Box 213, Box 218)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 85)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 85, Box 218)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 85)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 147, Box 213)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 85)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 218)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 147)
    - Photographs (Box 85, Box 408)
  - Albert Van Luit Company Showroom, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 85)
  - Vanderbilt Residence, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 85)
    - Drawings (Box 85)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 85)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 85)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 85)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 85)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 85)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 85)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 85)
    - Photographs (Box 85)
  - Vassar Library, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 86)
  - Victor, Benjamin Office, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 86)
    - Drawings (Box 86)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 86)
  - Victor, Benjamin Residence, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 86)
    - Drawings (Box 86)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 86)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 86)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 86)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 86)
  - Victoria Hotel, 1948
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 86)
    - Drawings (Box 86)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 86)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 388)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 388)
  - Vietnamese Exhibit, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 86)
    - Drawings (Box 237)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 237)
  - Virgin Isles Hotel, 1950
    Job location: St. Thomas, Virgin Islands
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 87)
    - Drawings (Box 87)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 87)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 86–87, Box 388)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 87)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 86–87, Box 388)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 87)
    - Photographs (Box 412)
  - Wachovia Bank and Trust Company, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 87)
    - Drawings (Box 87)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 87)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 87)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 87)
  - Waldorf Astoria Hotel Ballroom
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 87)
  - Wallenburg Showroom, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 87)
    - Drawings (Box 87)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 87)
  - Walz, Frederick, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 87)
    - Photographs (Box 87)
  - Washington, George House, 1958
    Job location: Mt. Vernon, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 87)
    - Photographs (Box 87)
  - Washington Hebrew Congregation, 1967
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 88)
    - Drawings (Box 88)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 88)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 88)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 88)
  - Washington International Airport (See: Dulles International Airport), 1963
  - Weiss, Seymour Office, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 88)
    - Drawings (Box 88)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 88)
  - Weissberg Residence, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 88)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 88)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 88)
  - Weithorn Residence, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 88)
    - Photographs (Box 88)
  - Welch, Don Residence, 1957
    Job location: Tulsa, OK
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Box 89, Box 388)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 89)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 89, Box 237, Box 388)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 89, Box 237, Box 388)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 89)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 89, Box 388)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 89)
  - Westburry Inn, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 89)
  - Western Electric Bell Telephone Company, Inc. (See Also: Bell Telephone Laboratory)
    - Drawings (Box 205, Box 252)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 205, Box 252)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 205)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 252)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 252)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Box 89)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 89)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 89)
  - Westmoreland County Museum of Art, 1955
    Job location: Greensburg, PA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 89)
  - Westville Shopping Center, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Box 89)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 89)
  - Wheaton College, 1938
    Job location: Norton, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 89)
    - Drawings (Box 89)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 89)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 89)
  - Whitaker, Clark and Daniels, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 89)
  - Whitehall
    Job location: Palm Beach, FL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 90)
    - Photographs (Box 90)
  - Walt Whitman Shopping Center, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 90)
  - Wickliffe Presbyterian Church, 1958
    Job location: Wickliffe, OH
    Collaborator: Robert A. Little
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 90)
    - Photographs (Box 90)
  - Wiley, R.C. Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 90)
    - Photographs (Box 408)
  - Will Rogers Equestrian Statue (See Also: Rogers, Will Equestrian Statue)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 71)
  - Willard Gallery, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 90)
  - Willard Hotel, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
  - Williams College, Dining Hall, 1963
    Job location: Williamstown, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90, Box 133)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 90, Box 133)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 133)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 133)
  - Williamson Residence, 1961
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90, Box 155, Box 220)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 90, Box 155)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 220)
  - Wilmington Grand Opera House, 1967
    Job location: Wilmington, DE
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Photographs (Box 90)
  - Wolgin, Jack Office, 1968
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 90)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 90)
  - Jonathan Woodner Co.
    - Unidentified Material (Box 360)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 360)
    - Drawings (Box 360)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 360)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 360)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 24)
    - Photographs (Box 62)
  - Woodner, Ian
    - Unidentified Material (Box 360)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 360)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 360)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 360)
  - Wurzburger, Janet, 1964
    Job location: Pikesville, MD
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
  - Xerox Showroom, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 90)
    - Drawings (Box 159)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 159)
  - Yale Center for British Art (See Also: Paul Mellon Center for British Art), 1974
  - Yale University: Art Gallery, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 91)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 91)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 91)
    - Photographs (Box 91)
  - Yale University: Design Laboratory, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 91)
    - Drawings (Box 91)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 91)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 91)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 91)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 91)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 91)
  - Yale University: Kline Chemistry Lab, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 92)
    - Drawings (Box 92)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 92)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 92)
  - Yale University: Kline Geology Lab, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 92)
    - Drawings (Box 200)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 200)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 200)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 200)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 200)
  - Yale University: Lecture, 1962
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 92)
    - Photographs (Box 92)
  - Yale University: School of Architecture, 1974
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 92)
  - Yale University: Special Shelving Units, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 92)
    - Drawings (Box 92)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 92)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 92)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 92)
  - Yale University: Sterling Auditorium, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 92)
  - Yale University: Woolsey Hall, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 92)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 92)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 92)
  - Zale Corporation, 1968
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 409)
  - Unidentified
    - Drawings (Box 409)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 409)
- Professional papers, 1909-1978; Series II
  - Address books, Undated (Box 413, Folder 1)
  - Art sources for commission, 1959-1962 (Box 339, Folder 1-2)
  - Bibliography, 1960 (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Biographical material, 1910, 1943-1974, undated (Box 410, Folder 1-7)
  - Business cards, Circa 1940s (Box 410, Folder 8)
  - Catalogs, 1932-1968 (Box 339, Folder 4-15)
  - Catalogs, 1932-1968 (Box 340, Folder 1-16)
  - Contracts
    - 1959-1963 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Circa 1959-1965 (Box 410, Folder 9-11)
  - Correspondence
    - 1940-1969 (Box 341, Folder 2-12)
    - 1946-1977 (Box 410, Folder 12-19)
  - Day books and appointment books
    General
    Richard Kelly recorded daily appointments, activities, and events in both day books and appointment books.
    - 1940 (Box 413, Folder 2)
    - 1944 (Box 413, Folder 3)
    - 1947-1959 (Box 413, Folder 4-27)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 414, Folder 1-20)
    - 1970-1974 June (Box 415, Folder 1-13)
    - 1974 July-1976 May (Box 416, Folder 1-6)
  - Drawings and sketches, 1951-1965 (Box 342, Folder 1-11)
  - Exhibition: "Light in Architecture", 1955 (Box 410, Folder 20)
  - Financial records
    - General, 1963-1967, undated (Box 410, Folder 21-22)
    - Bank books, bank deposit receipts, 1951-1959 (Box 343, Folder 1-15)
    - Bank books, bank deposit receipts, 1960-1961 (Box 344, Folder 1-3)
    - Business expenses, 1961-1966 (Box 344, Folder 4-6)
    - Carryovers
      - Billed, 1954-1961 (Box 344, Folder 7)
      - Unbilled, 1959-1960 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Invoices and correspondence, 1971, 1975 (Box 410, Folder 23)
    - Leases, 1962, 1965 (Box 410, Folder 24-25)
    - Ledgers, 1958-1966 (Box 410, Folder 26-27)
    - Receipts, accounting registers, 1952-1960 (Box 344, Folder 9-13)
    - Time allocation sheets, 1959-1963 (Box 345, Folder 1-4)
  - Information requests, 1960-1964 (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Lighting
    - General
      - 1940-1965, undated (Box 410, Folder 28-29)
      - Undated (Box 412, Folder 8)
    - Light damage factor, 1964-1971 (Box 410, Folder 30)
    - Lighting designs, 1966, undated (Box 410, Folder 31)
      Includes information about lamp designs by Richard Kelly.